{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Is she there? ' ______'",
      "a": "I'm afraid so",
      "b": "I fear yes",
      "c": "I'm afraid yes",
      "d": "I fear that yes",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is it raining. 'I'm _____'.",
      "a": "afraid so",
      "b": "afraid",
      "c": "afraid yes",
      "d": "afraid if",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is already nine o'clock, come on ______!",
      "a": "get up",
      "b": "you get up",
      "c": "get up you",
      "d": "don't gel up",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ making that noise!",
      "a": "You stop",
      "b": "Stops you",
      "c": "Stop you",
      "d": "Stop",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you think the weather will be good? 'I think _____'",
      "a": "that yes",
      "b": "yes",
      "c": "so",
      "d": "if",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Darling, ______that!",
      "a": "don't",
      "b": "don't do",
      "c": "you don't do",
      "d": "don't you do",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Soldiers, ______ fire yet!",
      "a": "don't open",
      "b": "not open",
      "c": "open not",
      "d": "you don't open",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is she there. 'I ______'.",
      "a": "don't think so",
      "b": "think not",
      "c": "don't think",
      "d": "think yes",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Hope/ think/ afraid/ say +so: used to refer back to an idea, action, quality, situation etc that has just been mentioned",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "OK, boys, ______ with me!",
      "a": "you come",
      "b": "come you",
      "c": "comes",
      "d": "come",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The children are in bed, _____ a noise!",
      "a": "don't do",
      "b": "don't make",
      "c": "doesn't make",
      "d": "doesn't do",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}